Finding Aid for Fred Newton Scott papers, 1860-1931
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Day-books
  - Miscellaneous notebooks and journals (Box 3)
Jan. 20 & 29, 1923, Mar. 9, 1923, May 21, 1923, Sept. 11, 1924, Sept. 14, 1924, June 30, 1925, Sept. 14, 1925, Mar. 30, 1926, Apr. 6, 1926, Nov. 30, 1926, Dec.7, 1926
Feb. 18, 1927, July 5, 1927, Dec. 12, 1928, Apr. 13, 1929, Dec. 9, 1929
Whitman, Charles E.
Apr. 2, 1928
Wilcox, Delos F. (Delos Franklin), 1873-1928.
Dec. 5, 1897, May 10, 1898